{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "oau",
      "description": "aojoajgoija",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "agfagasgf",
      "description": "testing time",
      "id": 4,
      "cards": []
    },
    {
      "name": "adsfq",
      "description": "ayrtyhsgbs",
      "id": 5,
      "cards": []
    },
    {
      "name": "asfq34fwaf",
      "description": "2awrgfaerg a",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "name": "fq34awr",
      "description": "qfvawrfgawrfg",
      "id": 7,
      "cards": [
        {
          "front": "1",
          "back": "oiuaojaovnao",
          "deckId": 7,
          "id": 9
        },
        {
          "front": "2",
          "back": "apisfjopadnfoan",
          "deckId": 7,
          "id": 10
        },
        {
          "front": "3",
          "back": "asfdaetrgeg",
          "deckId": 7,
          "id": 11
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "name": "gsdfgasfd",
      "description": "fa jdtyjdrth sra",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "name": "setgset",
      "description": "ethsetywh ",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "name": "new test",
      "description": "made form into it's own file and rendered it to edit card and add card. Testing time",
      "id": 10
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "tjrtye",
      "back": "erneynetyne",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?\n<Route>\n  <NotFound />\n</Route>",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all URL's",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "afdkjoj``",
      "back": "jaoaomoag",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "name": "asfq34fwaf",
      "description": "2awrgfaerg a",
      "id": 6,
      "cards": [],
      "front": "asfgar",
      "back": "gwergaerfae b",
      "deckId": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "1",
      "back": "oiuaojaovnao",
      "deckId": 7,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "2",
      "back": "apisfjopadnfoan",
      "deckId": 7,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "3",
      "back": "asfdaetrgeg",
      "deckId": 7,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "1",
      "back": "testing 1",
      "deckId": 10,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "2",
      "back": "second try at this\n",
      "deckId": 10,
      "id": 13
    }
  ]
}